fresh.com 2018-06-29

# Fresh - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Fresh.com (the “Website”) is published and maintained by Fresh, Inc., with offices located at 19 East 57th Street, New York, NY (“Fresh,” “we” or “us”).

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information on or through the Website and when applying for or using your membership in the Fresh Family Rewards Program (the “Membership”) in our retail store locations. By visiting this Website or applying for Membership, and/or using the services offered on or through this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, you should not use this Website or apply for Membership. As we update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Website Terms of Use, which governs your use of this Website. You can read our Terms of Use by clicking _**[here](https://www.fresh.com/customer-service-links/TermsOfUse.html).**_

This Privacy Policy only applies to Personal Information (as defined below) that we collect through this Website and your online interactions with us via email, online forms, or other online communications as well as Personal Information you provide to us, or that we may obtain, in person at one of our retail stores, provided that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information that you provide in one of our public or interactive areas of the Website (see the “Public and Interactive Areas of Our Website; Ratings & Reviews” section below). This Privacy Policy also does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain, other than through this Website or in person at our retail stores, such as by phone, through postal mail or through other live and print media. We may interact with you on third party sites where we post content or invite your feedback, such as Facebook or Twitter. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy policies of these third party websites. You are responsible for viewing and abiding by the privacy policies and terms of use posted on these third party sites. See also “Links to Third Party Websites” below).

You may opt in or opt out of our sharing of your personal information with third parties for marketing purposes by following the directions in the “Your Right to Opt In and/or Opt Out” section below.

Fresh does not knowingly collect or use any personally identifiable information from individuals under the age of 13. If we become aware that any such information has been provided or submitted to us, we will delete the information as soon as possible.

What information is Collected

Personal Information Your privacy is important to us. Depending on how you use the Website, we may ask you to share Personal Information with us. “Personal Information” includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone number; credit card and other payment information; birth day and other demographic information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual.

Fresh will ask you for information, including some Personal Information, if you complete a Customer Information Card in one of our retail stores or use one of several services on our Website:

• Sign up for e-mail: In order to receive our e-mail blasts, you need to share your e-mail address. You do not have to sign up for e-mail to browse the Website and make purchases.

• Becoming a registered user: In order to register, you need to share some Personal Information, such as your e-mail address. You do not have to be a registered user to browse the Website or make a purchase on the Website. If you want to use any of our interactive services, such as Ratings & Reviews services, you will need to become a registered user (if you aren't one already) and any personal information you submit will become part of your profile, as maintained by us.

• Applying for Membership in Fresh Family Rewards Program: In order to apply for and participate in our Fresh Family Rewards Program, you need to share some Personal Information, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address and your birth day and month. No purchase is necessary to be part of this program and you can sign up on the Website or in one of our retail stores. You do not need a Membership to visit the Website or to make a purchase on the Website. Once you have a Membership, you will have an account with Fresh tied to the e-mail address provided upon application. You can amend your information by (i) calling our Customer Service (see “Contact Us” section below) or (ii) signing in to Fresh.com using the e-mail address you provided upon application, going to the My Account page and following the instructions. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password.

• Making a purchase: When you buy something on the Website, you have to supply your name, a billing address, phone number, shipping address, and credit card information. If you become a registered user of the Website, you can choose to store information needed to make a purchase, such as your shipping and billing addresses in the “My Account” section. You can access this section using your registration login and password.

• Entering sweepstakes, contests, promotions and surveys: You may be asked to provide Personal Information in order to enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion, or answer a survey, on the Website. If you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or answer a survey, you will become a registered user (if you aren't one already). We may also ask you for some demographic information, such as your age. If you choose not to answer, you probably will not be able to participate in the sweepstakes, contest or survey. We may sometimes use a third party application on Facebook or other third party website to host a sweepstakes, promotion or contest. In those instances, the information you provide will be submitted to the third party and their privacy policy will govern the use and disclosure of the information you submit.

Website Usage Information

Cookies

We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive and can be used to collect information about where you travel on our Website and what pages you look at and items you purchase. They may store the information in your shopping cart, and/or your username and/or password. All of these purposes enable us to improve functionality and personalize your experience on our Website.

You can control how your browser handles cookies received from websites. You can choose to refuse all cookies, or to be prompted before a cookie is saved to your hard drive, or to only accept cookies from certain websites that you designate. By refusing to accept cookies from Fresh, you may not be able to use some of the features and functionality available on the Website.

For managing cookies and your choices, the configuration of each browser is different. Configuration is described in the help menu of your browser. For example, in Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.0 and above, you may block cookies by taking the following steps:

1\. Go to "Tools", then "Internet Options".

2\. Click on the "Privacy" tab.

3\. Use the cursor to select the level you require.

You can also click on Advanced for specialized cookie treatment.

Instructions for blocking cookies in other browsers are available at _**<http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/>**_.

Clear GIFs

We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “Web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, in the Website and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail that communicates to us whether you viewed an email that we sent you or visited a certain page on our Website. A clear GIF may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

IP Address and Clickstream Data

Our server automatically collects data about your server’s Internet address when you visit our Website. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Internet. When you request pages from our Website, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another website or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Website; the website you visit after this Website; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Website or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and internet service provider.

Third Party Ad Servers

We may use the services of one or more third party advertising companies. If we do, these third party advertising companies may also collect information from your activities on the Website as well as other sites for the purpose of providing advertisements and other content that is customized to your interests and preferences. This means that our ads may appear on participating web sites based upon your browsing activity. To allow us to offer our customers streamlined ordering and other useful features, we may use and allow our third party advertising companies to use the technologies listed above and other similar technologies.

Analytics

We may use Google Analytics to collect information about use of this Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often you visit this Website, what pages you visit when you do so, and what other websites you used prior to coming to this Website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this Website, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy, and we encourage you to read those Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to use other analytical tools similar to Google Analytics to collect the same types of information described above. You can prevent Google Analytics or other analytical tools from recognizing you on return visits to this Website by disabling cookies on your browser (see the “Cookies” section above).

Mobile Devices

You may be visiting our Website from your mobile device. Certain mobile service providers uniquely identify mobile devices and we or our third-party service providers may receive such information if you access the Website through mobile devices. Some features of the Website may allow for the collection of mobile phone numbers and we may associate that phone number to mobile device identification information. Furthermore, some mobile phone service providers operate systems that pinpoint the physical location of devices that use their service. Depending on the provider, we or our third-party service providers may receive this information.

Any or all of these activities regarding the Website usage information may be performed on our behalf by our service providers.

How is the Personal Information used?

We will use the Personal Information you provide to our Website in a number of different ways, including to: respond to your requests; process your orders; to provide you with information about our product and service offerings; anonymize and/or aggregate your Personal Information by combining it with other information; analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping and/or share it with our affiliates for internal marketing purposes. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you.

You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the “Your Right to Opt In and/or Opt Out” section below.

Do we share Personal Information and Website Usage information with others?

Third-Party Offers

We may provide you with opportunities to receive offers from other entities including our affiliates who have services, products and offers that we think might be of interest to you. Unless you elect not to receive such offers by following the instructions in the “Your Right to Opt In and/or Opt Out” section below, we may from time to time provide your Personal Information to these entities so that they may send you these offers. If you change your mind and no longer want us to share your Personal Information with these types of third parties, follow the instructions to opt out in the “Your Right to Opt In and/or Opt Out” section below.

Service Providers

We may use third-party partners to help operate our Website and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Website or for our business (such as Website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, credit card authorization companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, customer survey companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). We may combine information that you give us with other personally identifiable information from third-party sources to make our marketing efforts more efficient, including updating delivery and address information, which we use to correct our records.

Aggregate Statistics

We may disclose statistics, in the form of aggregate data, to third parties. This aggregate data may contain information regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and emails such as overall patterns or demographic reports. The aggregate data will not describe or identify any individual user.

Legally Compelled Disclosures

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Additionally, we cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property rights and other rights.

Business Transfer

In the event that Fresh is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, or if Fresh sells or otherwise transfer our assets or operations, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

"Wish List" functionality

You can send your Wish List to your friends. You will be asked to complete the following fields: names and email address. We will also ask you to provide the name and email address of your friend, to enable us to send them the information. We only collect this data for the purpose of sending your email. Recipient data is not saved or recorded.

Security

While Fresh will take reasonable precautions to protect the security and integrity of Personal Information provided to this Website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. No security measures are perfect or impenetrable. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different websites, and using up to date antivirus software. We maintain various physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. For example:

• We use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") authentication for online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the Internet helps protect your online transaction information from third party interception.

• We never display your full credit card number once it has been entered. We will only reveal the last four digits of your credit card for verification purposes.

• For additional security, we do not store your credit card number after processing your payment.

We urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone or share your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.

Unfortunately, despite all of our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all Internet use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.

If you contact us by e-mail or a “contact us” or similar feature on our Website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

If you choose to become a registered user or apply for a Membership, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Website by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify Fresh of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. It is your responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify Fresh when you desire to cancel your account on this Website. We are not responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision.

We will not be liable for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, and to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

Public and Interactive Areas of Our Website; Ratings & Reviews

We may from time to time provide interactive services on our Website, including, without limitation, Ratings & Reviews, blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards and discussion groups. Your use of such interactive services are at your own risk. Personal Information that you post on or through the public areas of the Website are generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others. You should not provide Personal Information about yourself in public or interactive areas of the Website. Such Personal Information is not covered under this Privacy Policy. For additional terms of using any of our interactive services, please see our Terms of Use located at [_**https://www.fresh.com/customer-service-links/TermsOfUse.html**_](https://www.fresh.com/customer-service-links/TermsOfUse.html)

California Do Not Track Disclosure

Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in some of their web browsers. This Website does not currently respond to Do Not Track signals, but we may do so in the future. For more information about Do Not Track, please go to _**[http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).**_ Third parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Website.

Consent to Processing

By providing Personal Information to this Website, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

Your Right to Opt In and/or Opt Out

You may have the right to “opt in” and/or “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Website, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to: (1) receive promotional correspondence from us, or (2) have your Personal Information shared with other entities for their marketing purposes. You may also edit your preferences by visiting the “My Account” Web page, e-mailing us at _**[mailpreferences@fresh.com](mailto:mailpreferences@fresh.com)**_ or calling our Customer Service (see “Contact Us” section below).

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.

Links to Third-Party Websites

Links on this Website to any third-party website (“Linked Site”) is provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave this Website. We are not obligated to review any Linked Site, do not control such Linked Sites, and are not responsible for any such Linked Sites (or the products, services, or content available through such site). We do not endorse or make any representations about any Linked Site, any information, software, products, services, or materials found there or any results that may be obtained from using such Linked Site. If you decide to access any Linked Site, you do so entirely at your own risk. The Linked Site may contain its own privacy policy and terms of use governing the collection and use of your information, and we are not responsible for the use of any information you submit to the Linked Sites. You are responsible for viewing and abiding by the privacy policies and terms of use posted on any Linked Site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Fresh reserves the right to change, revise or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Website by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Website. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by other means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Website or by sending you an e-mail.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at _**[inquiries@fresh.com](mailto:inquiries@fresh.com)**_ or call our Customer Service at 1 800 FRESH20 ( 1800 373 7420).

Effective Date: May 2014
